<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Container>
<Name>Pydio</Name>
<Support>http://lime-technology.com/forum/index.php?topic=39635</Support>
<Overview>Pydio (formerly AjaXplorer) is a mature open source software solution for file sharing and synchronization. With intuitive user interfaces (web / mobile / desktop), Pydio provides enterprise-grade features to gain back control and privacy of your data: user directory connectors, legacy filesystems drivers, comprehensive admin interface, and much more.</Overview>
<Description>Pydio (formerly AjaXplorer) is a mature open source software solution for file sharing and synchronization.[br]With intuitive user interfaces (web / mobile / desktop)[br]Pydio provides enterprise-grade features to gain back control and privacy of your data: user directory connectors, legacy filesystems drivers, comprehensive admin interface, and much more.[br][br][b]On first run of the container an ssmtp.conf file is placed in /config[br]Edit it with your details for email notifications to work (need to restart container to take effect)[/br]If you're not using mysql/mariadb, during setup you should select sqlite for db.[/br]At the end of installation it will give you the contents of an .htaccess file.[br]You must create it in the root of your mapped /var/www/pydio folder and then refresh the page.[/br][/br][b]A self signed SSL Certificate is generated the first time you run this container.[br]If you wish to use your own, place them in the /config/keys folder with same names as existing ones.</Description>
<Registry>https://registry.hub.docker.com/u/sparklyballs/pydio/</Registry>
<Repository>sparklyballs/pydio</Repository>
<BindTime>true</BindTime>
<Privileged>false</Privileged>
<Networking>
<Mode>bridge</Mode>
<Publish>
<Port>
<HostPort>6074</HostPort>
<ContainerPort>6074</ContainerPort>
<Protocol>tcp</Protocol>
</Port>
</Publish>
</Networking>
<Environment>
<Variable>
<Name>SUBJECT</Name>
<Value>/C=US/ST=CA/L=City/O=Organization/OU=Organization Unit/CN=yourhome.com</Value>
</Variable>
</Environment>
<Data>
  <Volume>
<HostDir></HostDir>
<ContainerDir>/UNRAID</ContainerDir>
<Mode>rw</Mode>
</Volume>
<Volume>
<HostDir></HostDir>
<ContainerDir>/var/www/pydio</ContainerDir>
<Mode>rw</Mode>
</Volume>
<Volume>
<HostDir></HostDir>
<ContainerDir>/config</ContainerDir>
<Mode>rw</Mode>
</Volume>
</Data>
<WebUI>https://[IP]:[PORT:6074]/</WebUI>
<Banner>http://i.imgur.com/BZoksFn.png</Banner>
<Icon>http://i.imgur.com/QdfVQrI.png</Icon>
</Container>
